Printing Office Printing Artifacts; null ua335.001
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Printing Office Printing Artifacts
1943-1975
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. Printing Office
ua335.001
1.0 cubic ft.
Contains halftone printing blocks depicting University buildings, faculty, and alumni created for the publication of the Alumni Quarterly.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Organizational Sketch
Printing blocks we used for images that were commonly featured in university publications.
Scope and Contents
Contains halftone printing blocks depicting University buildings, faculty, and alumni created for the publication of the Alumni Quarterly.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection has no series.
Printing--New York (State)--Albany.; UAlbany Communications & Marketing; State University of New York at Albany. Printing Office
- State Education Building, 6 x 3, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 1)
- Draper Hall and one section of Husted Hall and Hawley Hall, 2 x 4, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 2)
- Hawley, Draper, Husted, Richardson, Page and Milne Halls, 12 x 2, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 3)
- Draper Hall, front portico, 3 x 2 [oval], Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 4)
- Hawley, Draper, Husted, Richardson, Page, and Milne Hall, 11 x 2, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 5)
- Draper Hall, front view, 6 x 6, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 6)
- Minerva, 6 x 4, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 7)
- Page Hall, 6 x 7, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 8)
- Draper Hall, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 9)
- Draper Hall with part of Husted on the left and Hawley on the right, 6 x 5, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 10)
- Class of 1933 Gift Plate cut of window, 6 x 5 [added to collection 2/14/75], Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 11)
- Fireplace on the stage in the social room at Pierce Hall, 1 x 1 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. XVII, no. 3, Winter 1936, p. 17] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 12)
- Architect's Drawing of Brubacker Hall and Union, 7 x 2 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 31, no. 3, Jan. 1950, p. 2] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 13)
- Downtown Campus, north side building program, proposed [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 31, no. 3, Jan. 1950, p. 3] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 14)
- Arthur K. Beik, 1 x 2 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 31, no. 2, Oct. 1949, p. 12] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 15)
- Processional Moving-Up Day [Alumni Quarterly, vol. XXVII, no. 1, July 1944, p. 17] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 16)
- Dr. Albert N. Husted, 5 x 4 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. XXVII, no. 3, Jan. 1946, p. 3] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 17)
- Sayles Hall, 3 x 2 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. XXIV, no. 3, Winter 1943, p. 2] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 18)
- Commerce Building, 4 x 7 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 33, no. 2, Oct. 1951, p. 3] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 19)
- Pierce Hall - Stairway, 5 x 4, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 20)
- Willett Street Building, 1885, 4 x 3, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 21)
- Hawley, Draper, Husted, Richardson, Page, and Milne Halls, 9 x 2, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 22)
- New York State College for Teachers campus with Residence Hall, circa 1937, 6 x 4 (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 23)
- Round plaque, To Bertha E. Brimmer with great appreciation N.Y.S.C.T. Alumni Association, Albany, June 15, 1954, 2 x 2 (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 24)
- Draper Hall, front view, 8 x 7, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 25)
- Paul G. Bulger '36, 3 x 2 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 34, no. 4, Oct. 1953, p. 2] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 26)
- D. Emma Wilber Hodge '17, 2 x 2 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 26, no. 2, Oct. 1944, p. 4] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 27)
- Agnes Nolan Underwood '20, 2 x 2 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 26, no. 2, Oct. 1944, p. 5] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 28)
- Chester J. Terrell '27, 2 x 2 [Alumni Quarterly, vol. 26, no. 2, Oct. 1944, p. 4] (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 29)
- Statue of Minerva, 3 x 7, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 30)
- Minnie B. Scotland, 2 x 2, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 31)
- Dr. Alfred E. Husted, 4 x 3, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 32)
- Music Department, Nathan Gottschalk, Chairman... (plaque), 5 x 7, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 33)
- Music Department, Performing Arts Center, College of Arts & Sciences...(plaque), 5 x 7, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 34)
- Music Department, Performing Arts Center Faculty...(plaque), 5 x 7, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 35)
- Music Department, SUNY at Albany...(plaque), 10 x 7, Undated (Box 1 (Printing Office Printing Artifacts), Item 36)